[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "대한민국의\n수도는?",
    "choice1": "서울",
    "choice2": "부산",
    "answer": "서울"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "네팔의\n수도는?",
    "choice1": "포카라",
    "choice2": "카트만두",
    "answer": "카트만두"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "라오스의\n수도는?",
    "choice1": "싸완나켓",
    "choice2": "비엔티안",
    "answer": "비엔티안"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "미국의\n수도는?",
    "choice1": "워싱턴DC",
    "choice2": "뉴욕",
    "answer": "워싱턴DC"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "독일의\n수도는?",
    "choice1": "본",
    "choice2": "베를린",
    "answer": "베를린"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "베트남의\n수도는?",
    "choice1": "하노이",
    "choice2": "호치민",
    "answer": "하노이"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "중국의\n수도는?",
    "choice1": "상하이",
    "choice2": "베이징",
    "answer": "베이징"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "이탈리아의\n수도는?",
    "choice1": "로마",
    "choice2": "밀라노",
    "answer": "로마"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "스페인의\n수도는?",
    "choice1": "바르셀로나",
    "choice2": "마드리드",
    "answer": "마드리드"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "네덜란드의\n수도는?",
    "choice1": "암스테르담",
    "choice2": "로테르담",
    "answer": "암스테르담"
  }
]